The radiance of the night shines through my window
but the path to immortality is long.
The Eight Views and Nine-Bend Streams are desolate.
Living beings question the miseries of the world over a jar of wine.
Forget about Nirvana and rebirth,
I will break through the waves with my own flesh and blood.
The heavens are vast, so what if I was born mediocre ?
I stare at the Dao in my moments of madness
as the storm rages just below.
I've been thinking about life and death in my dreams.
I've unsheathed my sword to ask the immortals
why the world is a-changing.
Heaven and earth reveals its poignant truths.
Swallow the Four Seas and the Eight Wastelands,
experience all the vicissitudes of life in an instant.
I will defy the light in the sky
to continue to write a new chapter for all things in the three realms of existence.
Just a thought separates mortal from immortal.
Transform your insignificant body into light.
The hardships of the journey
will temper this young man's heart.
If I become a Renegade Immortal, will I hesitate to fight the heavens ?
Renegade Immortal
Subtitles by Bonobosubs
https://discord.gg/Ceckd4pdVA
The original body is here.
Master,
this purple core feels like a Nascent Soul.
It seems that the Divine Path
is the right way to breakthrough with the Ji Realm.
It's an upper Spirit Beast.
With my avatar's cultivation,
I couldn't see that its soul was still there.
Such hostility in his soul...
How painful was his death ?
Master,
it's about to dissipate !
Since we met before,
I'll save you.
From now on,
you're my third devil.
Junior Sister,
where are you going ?
Did something happen ?
Junior Sister,
you haven't answered yet.
What happened ?
Where are you going ?
Sun Zhenwei,
do you really think that
your Late stage Core Formation cultivation
is enough to stop me ?
If you don't step aside now,
then don't blame me for being ruthless.
Junior Sister,
this is the Cloud Sky Sect.
Why would I dare to stop you ?
You can go anywhere you want.
I'll be happy to accompany you.
Sun Hai
Early stage Core Formation
Little rabbit,
I already told you that
those girls are nothing but trouble.
You never listen !
Especially this girl,
she's very cunning.
She's not someone you can handle.
Are you happy now ?
I know you're frustrated
but I have no choice except restraining you for now.
The Eastern Courtyard has already sent word.
If you keep causing trouble,
they will shatter your cultivation.
That woman really is despicable.
They even sent an outer sect elder to kill me.
Come.
Kill me, I'm not scared.
If I blink,
then my name is not Cheng Xian !
I was indeed asked by someone to come
but to help you, not kill you.
Tell me,
what happened ?
Senior,
who asked you to help me ?
I will only give you 3 sentences
and that was the first one.
Cheng Ling from the Eastern Courtyard...
It's her fault !
She caused all this !
The real reason she got close to me
was because she was after my two Spirit Apes.
Were they yours ?
I know what Senior means.
There are many beasts in the Cloud Sky Sect
and they can be used for alchemy.
The beasts in the sect
are just tools.
But I brought them with me
when I joined the sect.
According to the Cloud Sky Sect's rules
those two belong to me.
So this Cheng Ling got close to you,
then asked for the two Spirit Apes.
You wanted to please her
so you handed them over to her.
Correct ?
But...
But I thought she wanted mounts.
I never thought her goal was their Core.
Big Ape
already got his Core removed !
Only Small Ape is left.
I went many times to get him back,
but I wasn't allowed inside.
It was an outer sect disciple
who hurt me.
I'm afraid that
my Spirit Ape is in danger.
This is weird.
Cheng Ling's cultivation is very low.
She can't need Beast Cores yet.
Someone else is behind all this.
Cheng Xian helped me before,
so I will help him
as much as I can.
What should I do ?
Please bring back
Small Ape.
Junior Sister,
what are you doing ?
I know you are here.
Why aren't you willing to meet me ?
Not even once.
Junior Sister,
who are you talking to ?
Wan'er doesn't ask anything else
but to see you once more.
Over the past 200 years,
I've been relying on the spirit liquid to keep my vitality.
But if you aren't willing to come out,
then Wan'er will kill herself right now.
To release myself
from this obsession.
Why are you like this ?
The moment your hand touches your bag of holding
is the moment you die.
Through the remnants of night, the Dao dreams
as years and seasons swirl unending.
This person is at Core Formation
but he gives off the feeling of a Nascent Soul...
Renegade Immortals cultivate thousands of years
to reach perfection.
Since Brother is Junior Sister Li's friend,
you are also the Cloud Sky Sect's friend.
If I was rude before,
it's a misunderstanding.
Pursuing immortality, understanding life and death, Karma and the Dao,
is very difficult.
Defying the heavens
requires resolve
Do you still have
that jade slip ?
I threw it away.
day after day, night after night,
through wind and snow, through this human life
Like a flying sword
soaring through the sky,
Since you threw it away...
Well, it wasn't anything valuable.
my aspirations are higher.
I'm leaving.
I will transcend
and break free from the reincarnation cycle.
Yet my love never grows old.
The Cloud Sky Sect Ancestors
want me to form a cultivation pair with this person.
I can turn into an Immortal
and defy the heavens
Before, I kept rejecting him...
but the flowers keep withering.
But now, I have no reasons left...
My love and resentment
are entangled in my heart
If you're still in the country in 3 months,
for this unrepentant vow.
then please come to the ceremony.
I have forgotten
what year it is
Congratulations.
but I cannot forget your face.
I can turn into an Immortal
and defy the heavens
but the flowers keep withering.
I hate you...
My love and resentment
are entangled in my heart
I hate you !!!
for this unrepentant vow.
Junior Sister,
he already left.
You bitch !
Note: Primordial Yin = virginity
Wait until I snatch your 200 years of Primordial Yin energy.
I will humiliate you
for rejecting me for so long !
As for this guy...
The Cloud Sky Sect Ancestors
want me to form a cultivation pair with this person.
If you're still in the country in 3 months,
then please come to the ceremony.
Master !
Master ?
Looks like his heart is in turmoil.
I'd better not disturb him now.
Sun Lingwu
Cloud Sky Sect Elder
Middle stage Nascent Soul
You can't come and go as you wish here.
Do you look down on our Cloud Sky Sect ?
Here comes a big problem !
He's obviously Nascent Soul.
You overestimate yourself.
You're looking for death !
Master, this old man is too strong.
We should leave while we still can.
Merge !
This is bad.
What's happening !?
Quick, protect the pill furnaces !
Master, I'm here. Save me !
Warn the Elders,
quick !
Little rat...
He won't come after us, will he ?
I've recovered my low cultivation.
No one will suspect me.
Follow Cheng Ling
and find out who's behind her.
Who ?
Me ?
Or, you can go and talk with the Nascent Soul guy.
It's up to you.
Master,
you're too weak for now.
I have to protect you.
Okay...
Junior Brother,
I have been ordered
to decorate the Northern Courtyard.
This is...
Your Grandmaster,
Elder Li Muwan
and Sun Zhenwei's marriage
is scheduled in 2 months.
The invitations have been sent out.
The sect has to be decorated as soon as possible.
Before, I kept rejecting him...
But now, I have no reasons left...
Master, Master !
Look !
I'm blessed.
Bad Senior,
I helped you to get the Spirit Ape to make pills.
Yet why are you marrying that old hag Li Muwan ?
What about Ling'er ?
I love you the most.
But Ling'er,
do you want to know why I have to marry that old hag ?
She has 200 years of Primordial Yin.
When I get her,
she will be nothing more
than my food
to help me reach Nascent Soul.
Are you still competing with her ?
Senior,
you're so mean !
I'll tell you
what I think of her.
How can anyone like her ?
She always wears a sad face
while pretending to be noble and pure.
Do you think she looks good ?
Kill them both.
Senior...
Okay !
What about us ?
Shit !
This is bad.
He has a defensive artifact.
By the way Master,
this guy has a Nascent Soul father protecting him.
It's the one we met earlier.
Someone !
Hurry, help !
He must die.
Disciple Wang Lin
pays respect to Grandteacher.
Your master is about to come out of seclusion.
If you have any questions,
just ask him when he comes out.
The Dual Cultivation Ceremony is approaching.
If I don't call you,
don't bother me again.
I want to improve my cultivation
to the level of Nascent Soul within 2 months.
Who...
Who are you ?
Is there such a pill ?
Who the hell are you !?
Killing Sun Zhenwei is easy.
But we have to wait
for my cultivation to be high enough so no one can oppose us
both in the Cloud Sky Sect and in Chu.
Sounds good ?
All individuals have a part of Yin and Yang but Yin energy is often associated with women / purity / cold. And Yang energy on the contrary is associated with men / warmth / fire.
Primordial Yin in a cultivation context means specifically the virginity of a woman that was preserved and contains immense energy / potential for a Yang-type individual. Dual cultivation is the way to harness both Yin and Yang in a complementary way through sharing both individuals' energy. In the event that one is stronger than the other, the weaker (generally the woman) will become the other's "cultivation furnace".
The term "cultivation furnace" is more widely used for any kind of exploitation of someone else to further one's cultivation.
I've had my share of wounds,
now I want to fight back.
Is my destiny a wall of restrictions
that's blocking all my hopes
for life ?
My flesh and blood witnessed the past,
my adversity pushed me to brave the waves.
How do you navigate through the years passing by ?
Nirvana and rebirth are no longer
out of reach.
Immortals
are obsessed with delusions of grandeur.
Renegades
seek to crush the impermanence of the heavens.
Don't tell me that I overestimate myself
and that the path to revenge leads to hell
because I don't see the harm in that.
My new body opens its eyes
and awakens from its dream.
I have overcome many trials
to get this body back.
No matter how many endless dark nights go by,
I can still see.
By sticking to this thought, I will get it done
by my own hands.
Returning to my body opened my eyes,
I need to continue my Immortal journey.
With a flick of a finger,
only my indomitable heart remains.
Life and death trials temper me, I am not afraid of losing my soul.
Even if there are countless tribulations and hardships.
Overcome this fate, smash through the obstacles,
like the descent of a god.